Oh Oh krispies in the ball going next in
double chocolate rice puffs chocolate
pop rice yes are you ready to Rio
look at this lovely lady Wow Wow wait I
think I'm gonna fart oh I lost that look
to the rescue now be careful we're very
close to equipment with a large jug God
get your large jugs away dude doing
around the bend for ya ha ha ha ha
and now commences the first annual
cereal war who shall win who shall die
or maybe it's just an exchange of
Technology and culture and everybody
wins it's a think tank of cereal really
ok let's start this quote-unquote war
going in Coco yeah mate 8 oh count
chuckle puffs oh my god I think I like
Coco the best unknown the whole world
it's like a Epcot yeah Epcot of cereal
you imagine if Disney world had a whole
area for cereal you know who would go
there Bevers no Lincoln no Hummer Jerry
Seinfeld
the guy from Seinfeld the main guy all
right what's the bleach situation and a
fridge like if you think that'll work
okay you can bleach it but you got to
water it down enough after it would be
best if you had one of the steamers if
they sell like on HSN this is so
disgusting Bevers rolled up all of my
Tupperware with this disgusting spinach
that has now all gone bad it's so gross
in here I could throw out everything
dude are you are you chewing something
yeah you got some like only cold um it's
so good oh dude check this out
oh my god the sound I can't deal with
this are you kidding
you're cleaning fake boobs I have a
issue with that dude it's like nuclear
waste you're gonna turn into Alex Mack
used Alex Mack from Nickelodeon she's
like neon statistically most people
enjoy gum you out of everyone I know
would like an oral fixation can you spit
it out honestly that is so gross
there's like ah oh my god did you have
fun tonight with your other friends you
better tell me now
you know better tell me now listen it
was just dinner in the theater districts
let's go to Times Square for dinner
Bruce you ever hear of the heart of
darkness she like entered the heart of
darkness
ever hear of it I live it every day dude
look at my like grandma lipstick on this
Jay it's good oh all my lipstick came
off because I there is like dude check
this out oh I love about this okay check
this out do you know that I'm in my
second trimester what are you having a
girl
Alana is that my baby is that what this
calls really about you have really
strong sperm that fights through birth
control yes Oh oh my god it's coming
Oh God oh my god look at her
Oh hold on what is all gooey all over it
Boop when did you put that all over her
um just before it are you jerking off
the head
no you massage your baby's head so it
gets round they're all squished from
your birth canal how do you know dude I
studied to be a doula alright quit but I
started to study wait Ilana I have one
calling all the basic calling
all the basic there's a new
announcement Shh
[Applause]
I know that I have a lot of Miss
connections but I just feel like this
one was really something special
I'm just want to make sure that this
draft is right just speak from the heart
you're always good at that
I'm just taking him through what exactly
happened we met at lush over the
boysenberry soap I got to make sure
that's spelled right I'm gonna I tell
that and then we both reached for the
same bar and then I said you take it and
then he said are you okay and I realized
I actually hadn't said anything because
it was like in my mind and I think he
would know that if I wrote it he's
paying attention to what I'm saying
I've never experienced this before what
are you doing dude
Oh what is that I think it's a bed bug
bite or something oh my god it's like an
ants meatball Ilana I think it's a
pimple would you help me purge it it
like really hurts on here I need your
help I'm lost in the woods here cystic
bacne woods all right let's just do it
horizontal or vertical squeeze I'd say
horizontal okay one out of ten how hard
should I squeeze it I would say ten okay
ready okay we got four hours until the
Sun sets we can do this we carbo loaded
last night let's go I know we're not
supposed to be this hungry we are
monsters I don't get Yom Kippur it sucks
it's like how is me waiting until the
Sun sets to eat this bacon egg and
cheese I'm gonna cancel out the time I
laughed in that hot dudes face about his
weird shaped nipples mid-coitus it's not
I am starving
jinx I think right now we're just
supposed to list like all the bad
we
this year until the Sun sets very Jewish
I've been taking my neighbors GQ
magazine's for four months they're
really hot I told these tourists the
other day the wrong directions I didn't
want them to know that I didn't know you
know sometimes I pray that the subway
breaks down or that there's a big
disaster in Midtown so I don't have to
go to work last week at the bodega the
guy gave me change and it was more money
than I gave him in the first place and I
kept it and I am a terrorist Abby what's
that picture bind you again it's Oprah
dude this is like the main thing in my
whole are you okay
yep I got something in my throat geez
and wish I had something in my throat
like food
I meant food like not like dicks just
not right now like it's just like a hard
thing to describe exactly why yeah you
have a complicated relationship with
it is complicated
it totally is it just depends on the
person it's like obviously it depends on
a lot of things like his personality is
penis Lil Abner yeah I Beulah I because
I'm just staring at you I'm right what
can you go look out the window and tell
me what the world is like mmm do we do
it myself
Ilana all right but you owe me big-time
mmm
people still exist Ilana are you eating
right now
no I feel weak oh nothing I'm gonna
faint I don't have to eat the rest of
the day if that's what you need no what
are we never gonna eat again I'm not cut
out for this and we're gonna throw these
away and then we're gonna feel terrible
about throwing them away and then we're
gonna have to atone for that we have to
eat this or else we're gonna have to
fast for not eating it
oh this is living I don't feel bad never
see that t-shirt with the evolution of
man what do you mean what don't you
understand the you said ma'am but you
did quotes oh it is the evolution of man
but it's just like women also exist what
the all right I got ya but it's
like monkeys are on all fours like dogs
and then heaps are like pretty chill and
then humans were like upright Homo
erectus double uh and then we go beyond
it you get hunched back over because
we're sitting at computers like us right
now I do not like that
me neither mm-hmm Shopko oh my god oh my
god Abbi get melody get melody she's
right here okay um mom's I was just like
I was kidding I just I'm not getting
good Frank
okay that was me
what was it nice I just like to love her
so much like does Jessica Lange just
happen to be super sexy or yeah do I
love her because she's so sexy that too
this is the difference between wanting
to be a woman and wanting to be in a
woman what do you mean wanting to be in
a woman Mike with I feel the same way
about guys like you want to be in all of
them not all of them and not like all
the time you tell me about being inside
a guy I'm not that kind of quiet well
that I am I get it though it's like
wearing a guy's shirt loved a shirt oh I
love a shirt it's like in middle school
when you wear a guy who likes baseball
cap or like heavy gold confirmation
chain of the cross on it are you joking
oh no I guess that's like the long
island version and the mainline version
is like an American flag ice bold cop
okay I did not say American flag you did
did not okay we got one minute left and
then we can scrape this off yeah
sort of burn but like that means it's
working
oh it's burning and working oh oh no oh
what a lot of what I
just closed my butt cheeks in it got the
cream inside my paw hole oh my god why
is it so close your butthole I have hair
there
should I get shelter and blast it up
there to cleanse it out I said the first
thing you thought of no don't put
Seltzer up your bod do I do
oh no I would not do so sir Oh oh my god
oh it's going into my cornea ah oh oh
here we go it's gonna be good
Oh eight highly dead chick don't smoke
to stay away hey dude what song is that
I wrote it no yeah that was really good
I thought it was Pearl Jam shut up yeah
no I did that is so dope where are you
going dude to work my friend Ilana it is
Columbus Day the National Day of not
doing do I need to sing my song
again I could also do it like in a lot
of different variations Abbi Abrams I
don't want to hear it at all
Christopher Columbus is the original
white douche he raped and
pillaged his way through America I'm not
gonna give his ghost the satisfaction of
getting me a day off so you're going to
work as like an act of protest do you
want to come no dude I'm not going to
your office on my day off okay I'm not
gonna like do work I'm just gonna like
check my email turn the lights on and
off print some do anything you want
me to print yes I have so much stuff I
have all these coupons I was thinking of
printing out some like hot pics of
celebs because screens are like really
starting to affect my eyes I totally get
that yeah send me send me anything I
really want to drain the ink and stick
it to Chrissy see you wanna I'm in
the air so when he doesn't grab his
heart pull it out and put his
mouth hey you know how we do I'd like to
scalp them and show them and be like
gotcha you should take his scalp
and you should like throw it down a
really steep hill and watch it go I
would be like I'm gonna give you head
and then bite his dick
no you would give Christopher Columbus
head only to bite it yeah but I'm not
I'm gonna be there very long if you want
to get a drink after yes let's drink to
like something really significant like
the real hero Christopher Columbus who
directed home I love that idea I don't
even know where I'd
this I've never worn this donate okay I
feel like this is like rude to donate
you'd have to cut around the sweat
stains and repurpose the cotton
oh my gosh dude I bought these when I
was like really in the top chef I
thought I wanted to be a chef for a
second okay it's not oh
donut donut dude yeah my mother's donate
Alana my box of pastel sweaters gross do
not ever let me go back to that life
again I will not let you down donate
[Music]
donate ever never donate not I had no
idea what you're gonna say but I knew
what I was gonna say it is in a son when
people wear heels on Halloween in the
city it's insane to wear heels in the
city knock on Halloween it's insane she
put sneakers on it's like a holiday for
which I'm all for no me too I can
be a sometimes like a lot maybe we
just don't need Halloween to express our
sluttiness is all and hey good for you
if you do it's just cold out
okay are you ready I'm sorry I've been
ready go go go wait for it you wait for
it I'm changing
oh I'm changing I'm a changing harder
than you've ever changed and here we go
what are we best friends or are we best
friends okay how did we not consult that
we were both going to be victorious RBG
Oh Wow Ruth Bader Ginsburg does
deserve both of ours homage I am Yosh
you Hootie
good shootie oh wait huh
Oh hold on here we go watch out world
cuz I'm about to make a lob pass that's
important for Humanity and women that is
so baller muumuus get a bad rap I'm so
cozy I know first of all they are
elegante second of all I have Aaron out
my here I feel healthier than ever
on oh my god I'm stuck I'm stuck in
an elevator that you're in an elevator
why would you go into a big building
today of all days I know I'm sorry okay
my laser hair removal I mean it is about
to get I am Legend up in here you're
gonna need those I know dude when I
prepaid for the package what am I not
gonna finish a package I'm sorry I don't
want a mustache for the apocalypse
mustaches are gonna be currency soon I
mean it's gonna grow back Lee's really
hardly works on me I know I think it's
not like the equipment and the settings
more importantly okay okay okay it's
happening we are t-minus 60 seconds
until is inaugurated I can't believe it
oh my god okay okay you know what your
your elevator we'll meet somewhere in
the middle okay okay I hate that spot
but okay all right now do you have nice
yeah
do you have your butterfly knife yeah
it's in my other hands good okay okay
we're 30 seconds wrap oh I love you and
on the way if you could loot you know
batteries or food I kind of forgot I
forgot matter is nnk 15 seconds I got
eyes nose throat eyes most Oh neat
asteroid feet okay three two
[Applause]
elevators just working like they never
found down here nothing does I can't see
I want to go check it out woman hating
Twitter he's a time poverty
measure
brag about sexual assault
people are just gonna be grabbing shape
dude pants he's like a on wooden
doll from the 50s we're cops now people
are just gonna be peeing on other people
me man boo me at the mouth now in a
verse part is that he's actually sick
he's just mentally ill it's not even
funny
[Music]
so I'm just gonna come over still yeah
and you know we'll just Google how to
Google our local representatives okay
good plan today hopefully okay I'll see
you a little bit muggy baby whoo April
baby okay so I just saw him this site
that rhubarb's are in season now finally
I'm gonna make a pie I thought you
wanted to make pie are you alright
I have to say something at me it's hard
to say but I just feel like we've been
hanging out too much lately I mean it's
been like it oh the time every
day are we even individuals anymore you
know are we just one fused brain we've
reached a tipping point and is the
hardest part but I think we need a break
a friend break where we take a week off
of talking texting phone conversation
and even IRL hangs no letters no cards a
friend break just for a week you know
what I kind of been feeling the same way
I think this is a really great idea we
did the same April Fool's oh my god I
feel even closer we got a hangout every
day forever other words gonna blow my
brains out Shh
not if I blow mine out first oh okay I'm
coming over what sounds great see you
soon really didn't you this masked ball
ha did you start already - we have this
whole planet no kill girl
it's my aroma diffusor I took at that
lavender rosemary and put in
100% babe oil holy dude that's
genius happy holidays
oh yeah holidays with a Z no no I got it
ok are you ready to rumble
[Music]
ok races
wait Ilana where's your bowl I don't
know
[Music]
all right I got a stain on my
button-down I have an interview today I
need to get out right now things just
like no titty do you want the job or do
you don't waste your time I need to get
the stain out Wow
not gonna get it out like that dude I'm
sorry it just cost me 58 bucks
what was the thing that your grandmother
used to do the secret trap tomato juice
juice of tomahto tomato juice you sure
yep all right let me see hold on God I
love weed okay
all right I don't have tomato juice but
I have Bloody Mary max oh that's even
better the horseradish will exfoliate
stain awesome okay here we go okay so do
I do I rub it in yes rub it in smart
good it's like was it working I don't
know if it's making it look better wait
you did you applied did I put the yeah
you just watched me do the whole thing
hey just remember that that was the
wrong trick tomato juice is for skunk
sprays are you keep you know what I
realized her trick was couple drops of
detergent on the stain and then you let
it sit and then you wash it normally do
you have time for that her trick was
pre-treating a stain we all know how to
pretreat a stain grandma hey turn that
pout inside out sister cuz you know what
they have no choice but to show your
freakin titties and that's how you're
gonna get a damn job in this city
town you think I could go like
this go like this take the pants off I'm
going to interview to be a docent at the
Frick yeah well your ass is more
powerful than your tits sorry let me
just get my bag and then I have to go oh
yeah there it is
hmm get that job edge you know what I am
gonna get that job you know why cuz I
love the Frick bend over a bunch
you loose warming it up okay so let's
get the air out dude why don't you just
buy the mr. crazy like that well I
obviously spent so much on the outfit
that I think it's irresponsible to also
subscribe to an entire app okay alright
so you're just gonna watch me yes so you
watch the video on the app I'll watch
you it's like a game of telephone but
with our bodies okay alright are you
ready to move with mr. crazy lug Yas
whoa okay Rob jump kicks here we go
alright they're moving into here through
that perfect so I'm really trying to
mimic the instructor good I'm mimicking
you and that's how this works right love
it
dude I love the way your ponytail whips
yeah I wish you could just go topless
and just forever all the time
dude like I don't like this commentary
sorry okay here we go
Ray's cam homework I say from the side I
don't understand the form with the block
lugging so it's like you you're up and
then you drink you're up and then the
Campbell drink Wow okay sees you stick
your butt out like that in your chest
yeah and then you really use your core
and then you spread the bone the bone
nice Brenham
like I get it you got that a
killer yeah God I got it good do you
need me to move closer I got to see the
bath a little more well it's just like
right left you know yeah and so you
should feel it in your core I've done
this to old for bongs do them too old
for bombs
ah okay so we've the same exact deck in
the same exact order so your top two
cards should be ten of clovers and king
of black tears I have club I guess you
say clubs I think clovers committed two
Moto's and then a king of black tears
what's that you mean the Spade with a
spade a spade like it's like this shape
yeah looks like a black tear well a
Hershey kiss somebody's nose
that is weirdly accurate don't steal it
out baby okay I hope we did it right
dude the king of black tears and I have
a Jokers I took all the Joker's out of
my deck that's just a rule of my family
because those are like wilds and no I
have the ten of clubs
what's clubs clovers right to my day -
my day weekend Timmy
hmm oh wait who's this Tim milk - Tim
Curry Nanny McPhee oh no no okay yeah
let me just play solitaire individually
and just Tom we can only play solitaire
online because it low like yeah cards
like um you know I mean their lattice
buying thing G is it out yeah uh-huh
yeah you just act you know like what
that makes you feel like don't be mad
dude but I just I'm just sitting here
with my vibrator
I'm not vibrating it's not inserted we
have had this conversation before about
how I would like to know when that was
going I'm not building up to something
this is not does not have a narrative -
it's the same as if I had a heating pad
I have a heating pad on the small of my
back right now
well you're also a pervert and then we
need a second to think about this okay
I'm really sorry I betrayed your trust
it's all right I'll talk to you in like
a little bit mmm right boy wanna see
[Music]
happy through need a really though have
you ever had such a healing tradition as
they're so healthy and so smart you go
first by day okay here we go
massaged kale we got some boobs
otherwise known as blueberry looks like
blue boobs like getting blue boobed
banana sweet low-fat yogurt ice and I'm
going to tell you it looks yummy I
should get started on mine
starting with yams and do some black
fairies that makes the smoothie
expensive bee pollen he Polly that I
live forever
where you going the farmers market ice
witchy and coconut water
I'm Rihanna ooh electrolytes the
most important thing maca what's maca
turn on the blender
[Applause]
[Music]
you know looking at mine it looks a
little chunky
you know what mine's not chunky enough
[Music]
[Applause]
good looks great drink up my dears we
have a perfect friendship we really do
happy fourth of July and ma'am
whoa whoa careful yes are you ready
to do this contest cuz it is every
year and it's like the only reason why I
feel I still am an American despite the
current administration are you ready
yeah I was just gonna say I've where you
got in your whole thing like I don't
know if I can do it does something
happen are you I didn't boil in the dogs
and I was smelling out that hot water
don't tell me boiling the dogs didn't
make you want the dogs more it didn't I
don't want two dogs
okay been doing this for a couple
usually do this isn't fun for me you
know I'm not gonna let it get me down I
guess I'll just compete against myself
yeah dude this is your thing you are
gonna kill it I have seven here today
that's all I need to beat my own record
I'm gonna be your old man
Rafi old man you got this dude I'm gonna
watch you as much as I can you are
skilled if you're amazing you are my
best friend for a reason and it's right
now you are the representative of our
country us at your Liberty
[Music]
okay no gagging dump it then I'll make
it go you having fun
go drink the dog water don't drink the
salt water you good Pete my record just
finding it and how's that yes that's
perfect you just stay right there
this is poor Donna you're the one that
wanted me to draw your portrait like
what do you think this was gonna be like
I thought it might be like a little fun
okay well just hold it still okay okay
your are my nipples hard capturing that
that's a card with overalls but I wanna
seriously oh oh yeah yeah here we go
wanna have you ever heard of continuity
okay have you ever heard of a bitch's
hair was in her eyes am I supposed to be
naked for this the answer now and
forever is no you should not be naked
okay listen you watch your tone of
delivery I'm sorry okay I'm done
okay I'm so excited to see you okay I
hope you like it dude
hi des it's aspirational for my nipples
- thank you I love it
the stuffing is my favorite part
oh my I mean it's just like a pile of my
little pieces of bread like densely
packed together what's not to love the
way you describe is so beautiful
Thanks mm-hmm okay so you're ready to
Show and Tell BAE BAE oh yeah Small
Business Saturday we're like really
doing it up this year it is so important
to support local businesses so as I was
browsing the shops on lick canals the
guianese the Gowanus Canal mm-hmm I
stopped in to a local pottery shop and
got this piece to support the local
artisans I guess it's a mug you could
use it for a variety of things yeah I
put my penis in this if I was a boy look
I'm nosing it okay you ready for this
yep I didn't go to Lowe's I didn't go to
Home Depot I didn't go to hardware town
USA I went to my local Zeb's hardware
store and I got this hose because one
day I'm gonna be one of those fancy
people that has that wide selection of
like dope plant life on my fire escape
and when I am I'm going to use this hose
to keep those bad boys alive I'm genius
inspiring and good for the world thank
you okay this auto shop near me also
makes neon signs for other shops
check this out oh my gosh one it creates
the perfect ambience great font - it's a
refreshing spin on a sad lamb great vibe
and three it's a friendly suggestion
great directive thank you you did good
we are really participating in our
community Oh total and you know what all
this small business shopping we earned
Cyber Monday oh I cannot wait to just go
like this
boom god I miss Amazon just scrolling
you know it brings my heart rate down
how much do you think this hose is if I
bought it on Amazon it's not like a
local made hose that's right right and
it's like I'm buying something local and
yet it was like made somewhere else you
know I mean oh you say with a C oh btw I
add the CC is for Wow okay you open
yours first no come on you open yours
first no you go Phil you go first
dude please open your gift first okay I
can't say no to that face look five four
three two one
Chanukah oh my god slow cooker are you
serious this is high high quality you
like it I don't like it bench I love it
yes I'm gonna marinate meat for hours
and hours and hours and hours all the
live long day I just figured since
you've been so into bone broth dude it's
so thoughtful and adult I really
appreciate it thank you so much okay now
it's your turn here we go you are going
to love it
do you love it yes yes I I do i I mean I
love it I was just like what do you get
the girl who already has everything and
this just popped into my head this did
mm-hmm it doesn't come with battery so I
wrap some in tobacco leaves for you
they're also in there there they are and
there's a sample of water-based cleanser
do not wash it with soap it will
deteriorate and start to peel I wouldn't
have thought to like wash it huh I will
follow those instructions to take good
care of this oh my god dude I'm running
late I gotta go okay love you baby love
you happy Hannukah you too thanks for my
thing some people are intimidated by
growing hands but it's actually very
simple
don't get frustrated you can do this
okay hmm mom I am pescetarian now hello
Abbi Ilana oh my god where are you dude
there you are did you hear before yeah
what you've been eating dude what's
going on it veggies make sense
make sense yo where have you been
texting and emailing and calling what
happened after the portrait we lost you
you were wandering in the party looking
for more credit more kind of
that's an internet drug okay shh shh
you're you're asking me dude I just woke
up and he was next to me in bed okay
okay we'll figure this out together for
you spooning yeah but were you bigger a
little okay I just woke up and this dude
was in my bed I have no idea who he dig
or little big
okay tell me a little bit about your
experience with him was there for play
was it good did he think of the four
player did you have to request it did
you fondle his balls they understand why
that information would be necessary
right now okay Abby
not all men like or want ball fondling
okay sometimes they want to tug
sometimes they want to rakes and doesn't
want to squeeze and as they want a
little tickle I'm just trying to narrow
it down to see if we know idle or not
okay so fine I grab his wallet out of
his back right pocket of his jeans
what do you trust me do it hey um whoa
dude how did you know that you know all
men are the same to an extent are these
guys it's got a lot of cash you mean
he's rich but a coffee punch cards my
kind of guy right okay this is that my
wallet hey that's my Christmas money
what's his name what's his name uh or
another okay is your person a man you
know they they might be gender
non-binary okay hmm you know you go okay
is your person assists straight white
probably skinny dict cog in the machine
of the suffocating heteronormative
patriarchal misogynistic value trip in
judeo-christian military-industrial
complex uh I mean I don't I don't think
he's white but I'm not sure like I
shouldn't assume yeah better Nance yeah
okay okay okay is your person wearing
any sort
accessory I mean are we including
procedures meant to protect the gender
nonconforming from hate speech based
solely on appearance
I just meant like earrings
oh no okay yes babe a two down here we
go okay
all right is your person yes okay you
know what I think we're good here
yeah yeah I feel good I feel good I had
max I had Anita so um good game I'll see
you later bye bye
[Music]
you